{
    "subject": "resource/Timothy_Dalton",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:British_male_television_actors",
    "human_readable": "Timothy Dalton is a subject of Category:British male television actors.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.964621365070343,
            "question": "Is Timothy Dalton a British actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8583204746246338,
            "question": "Name some notable British male television actors."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.825675904750824,
            "question": "Has Timothy Dalton appeared in television shows?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8127284049987793,
            "question": "Can you give examples of other actors in the same category as Timothy Dalton?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8021087646484375,
            "question": "To which category does Timothy Dalton belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7959274649620056,
            "question": "What type of acting is Timothy Dalton known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.729729950428009,
            "question": "What is the significance of being a British male television actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6918302774429321,
            "question": "What are some characteristics of British male television actors?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.669629693031311,
            "question": "Are there any famous roles played by Timothy Dalton?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6627069115638733,
            "question": "What is Timothy Dalton's profession?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Timothy Dalton is a subject of Category:British male television actors.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5429_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous roles played by Timothy Dalton?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5429_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some characteristics of British male television actors?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5429_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the significance of being a British male television actor?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5429_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5429_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5429_122.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5429_146.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5429_174.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5429_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5429_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5429_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5429_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5429_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5429_82.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, I can answer your query as follows:\n\n`{ \"output\": \"no\" }`\n\nThe reason for this response is that while Timothy Dalton is indeed a British actor who has appeared in various films and TV shows, including playing James Bond, there is no explicit mention of him being categorized under Category:British male television actors. The documents provide information on his career, notable roles, and awards, but do not specifically state that he belongs to this category."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Timothy Dalton being an actor and his notable roles, which supports the statement that he is a subject of the category \"British male television actors.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "Timothy Dalton has had a film career as well.",
            "category": 4
        }
    }
}